filepan.com 2012-06-02

# Terms & Privacy: FilePan.com: Free Search and Download Video, Audio, Games, Software and More!

Users of 18 years or under must be supervised by an adult of at least 19 years when using FilePan.com. For users at or under the age of 18 using FilePan.com under the supervision of an adult of 19 or above, please leave this site if you open a webpage that contains materials which may offend or may not be distributed, circulated, sold, hired, given, lent, shown, played or projected to a person of your age. 

We woud like to take this opprotunity to declare that all the files and resources whose links and/or names appear in FilePan.com are stored or contained in external servers that are neither endorsed by nor related to, whether directly or indirectly, FilePan.com. We are against infringement of intellectual property in any form or manner. Please report to us immediately any links in FilePan.com that direct to unauthorized and/or unlicensed contents. 

It is our policy to respond to any infringement notices and take appropriate actions under the **Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA)** and other intellectual property laws whichever applicable. If your copyrighted material has been posted unintentionally on FilePan.com or if links to your copyrighted material are returned through our file search engine and you want this material removed, you need to provide a written communication that details the information listed in the following section. Please be aware that you will be liable for damages (including costs and attorneys' fees) if you misrepresent information listed on our site that is infringing on your copyrights. 

The following elements must be included in your copyright infringement claim: 

  1. Provide sufficient contact information so that we may contact you. You must also include a valid email address.
  2. You must identify in sufficient detail the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed and including at least one search term under which the material appears in the search results returned by FilePan.com. 
  3. A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
  4. A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
  5. Must be signed by the authorized person to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly being infringed. (Electronic signature accepted)

To expediate the processing of your copyright infringement claim, please email your written infringement notice to admin[at]filepan.com (please manually replace "[at]" with "@"). 

We inform you that, although best efforts have been made, we cannot guarantee that all contents will be deleted immediatelly upon your request due to the large volume of requests we receive and the delay associated with the scheduled update process of our file search engine. Please send us a valid link to each search result which contains your copyrighted material, such that we can completely remove all the contents related to your material. 

Please allow 3-5 business days for an email response. Note that emailing your copyright infringement claim to other parties such as our Internet Service Provider will not expedite your request and may result in a delayed response, as your claim may not be directed to us promptly. 

## Customer information:

Necessary customer information is collected for the purpose of providing better quality of service solely. Some of the collected information is known as nonpublic personal information. FilePan.com has no need to seek or collect nonpublic personal information from any third party sources. FilePan.com strives to maintain accurate, up-to-date records in order to serve its clients. Any inaccuracies that are called to my attention are corrected promptly.

## Sharing information:

FilePan.com does not share nonpublic personal information with any outside persons or organizations. FilePan.com does not sell, rent, or loan its client list to any third party. FilePan.com does not give prospective clients the names of existing clients unless authorized in written form to do so.

## Access to and protection of information:

As required by law, only those governmental agencies with a valid reason for doing so have access to files on FilePan.com containing nonpublic personal information. FilePan.com maintains security standards to protect nonpublic personal information.

## Disclosure of privacy policy:

FilePan.com provides this privacy notice for informational purposes and will update it as required by law. Should you have any comments, suggestions or questions about the privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.

## Personally Identifiable Information

FilePan.com never collects your personally identifiable information except the email address when you register as a user of FilePan.com.

## Usage tracking: Collection of your IP Address:

Your IP address is a unique number used to identify your specific computer on a public network. FilePan.com may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, such as diagnosing problems with our server, to analyze consumer behavior and trends, and to audit the use of our site. IP addresses are not used to personally identify a customer and are kept anonymous. 

## Links to Other Web Sites:

Please be aware that when you click on links that direct you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to their respective privacy policy. While FilePan.com supports the protection of privacy on the Internet, FilePan.com cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the privacy statement whenever interacting with other web sites.

## Legal Disclosure:

FilePan.com may disclose certain account information in special cases when it has sufficient reasons to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating FilePan.com's terms of use or terms of service, or may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with any of FilePan.com's rights or property, other FilePan.com customers, or anyone else FilePan.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.
